

INFO

Name Brody Maclean

Address 38 Queen Street, Glebe NSW 2037

Phone 0401212399

Email hello@brody.com

Website brody.com

SOCIAL

Twitter twitter.com/brodymaclean

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/brodymaclean

CodePen codepen.io/brody

Github github.com/brody

Dribbbledribbble.com/brodymaclean

REFERENCES

Available upon request

BRODY MACLEAN

PRODUCT DESIGN LEAD

PROFILE

An experienced and enthusiastic Product Design Lead with a background in designing for web, mobile devices & MacOS, and a proven track record for initiative, problem solving and reliable hard work, who aims to further a career in Product Design. Synthesising the needs and goals of users, product managers, developers and testers to ensure the best possible experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER

THRED LIMITED | AUG 2017 - PRESENT

On top of rolling out a fresh product and iterating upon those designs, I've had the chance to create the Sweep.im website, Thred Investor Relations app & business portal CMS for our business clients.

LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER

CLOUDBEES / JENKINS | SEPT 2016 - AUG 2017

Applied research-based principles to drive the redesign of Jenkins. As the first designer, I led the building of the design team within the company establishing design principles and systems to help the team scale. Created the Sketch UI Kit & worked on the React components to roll designs across to code.

PRODUCT DESIGNER

HUDL | DEC 2015 - SEPT 2016

Led the redesign of elite sports analytics software that fully support end-user needs while achieving the business vision. Led user research and interface design processes creating personas, visualizations, wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and HTML prototypes.

DIGITAL / UX DESIGNER

FAIRFAX MEDIA (REGIONAL) | SEPT 2010 - OCT 2015

Designed the UX & UI for ~180 regional websites, iPhone apps & CMS.

EDUCATION

SKETCHING FOR UX, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT & UX

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, CODECADEMY & CODESCHOOL

Ongoing skills training to add to my tool kit to help create the best user experience.

DESKTOP PUBLISHING

ULTIMO TAFE

Visual communication, Adobe Creative Suite, typography & layout.